nikkibeach.com 2012-06-30

# Nikki Beach

## NIKKI BEACH

### Privacy Policy

**Your privacy is important to us**. 

This Privacy Statement covers personal information, non-personal data collection and aggregate reporting for the NikkiBeach website. 

**Collected Information**

Personal information is information that is associated with your name or personal identity.  Nikki Beach.com uses personal information to understand better your needs and interests and to provide you with better service.  Once you choose to provide us with personal information, you can be assured it will be used only to support your customer relationship with Nikki Beach.com.  We take seriously the trust you place in us.  Nikki Beach website will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. 

In some areas of our website, you can request information, subscribe to marketing or brochure materials, register yourself or your company for access to restricted areas, or apply for a job at Nikki Beach website.

The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and/’or contact preferences.  To personalize our websites, services or communications, we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, and experiences with our website or services.  Providing this additional information is optional.

Non-personal information is data about usage and service operation that is not associated with a specific personal identity.  Nikki Beach website collects and analyzes non-personal information to evaluate how visitors use the Nikki Beach websites.  Non-personal data we collect may include the pages visited on the Nikki Beach website, unique URLs visited within Nikki Beach Hotels.com, browser type and IP address.  Most non-personal data is collected via cookies or other analysis technologies.  Nikki Beach.com web pages use cookies and other technologies for data analysis and personalization services. 

**Children’s privacy**

Nikki Beach website is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests.  Nikki Beach website does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 nor target its website to children under 13. 

**How we use your information**

Nikki Beach  website uses your personal information to provide you with services, marketing and communications in relation to our resort, and to help us better understand your needs and interests.  Specifically, we use your information to provide brochures and information, to communicate with you, to update you on events and specials, to personal promotional offers and to enhance the Nikki Beach website. 

Non-personal data is aggregated for reporting about Nikki Beach website usability, performance and effectiveness.  It is used to improve the customer experience, usability and site content.    

**Who we share your information with**

Nikki Beach.com will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. 

**Opting Out**

Nikki Beach website will not use your personal information for a different purpose than the one stated when you provided your data.  To opt-out of receiving communications you have expressly requested (such as e-mail newsletters, promotions, etc.), please select the e-mail “opt-out” or “unsubscribe” link included in each subscription communication or by contacting us directly. 

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact [abuse@nikkibeach.com](mailto:abuse@nikkibeach.com)

| 

---|---
